So, let me show you how to crack the browser credentials like username and passwords from
any of the machine.
So, in this video I will be targeting the Chrome user credential data.
Let me have one of the command, okay, so this will be, I will be giving this a resource session,
so don't worry, okay.
So, you know how to execute from command and control machine probably will be getting a reverse
connection from, it was connection from a calling machine, right if you executing the
cobalt, right payload or if you executing some other payload side.
So, but I will be totally explaining in the Windows machine because the theory, the concept
is like the same, the technique is like the same, so you are going to follow a different
way, okay.
So, let me execute the PowerShell here and let me execute this command, so I am getting some
of basics for encoder has this was encrypted key, okay, for Chrome data credentials,
like this is an encryption key basically, okay, let's take this like encryption key and
we are using one of MIMICADs function called dpap is to is to Chrome and this is our directory
where the Chrome login data is like username and password will be basically stored in here
and we will be giving that encrypted key here which we have a grip from previous command,
like this one, this one here, okay, and we will be giving an unprotect, okay, so let me execute
this in a MIMICADs, okay, the copy piece was not working properly, so let me execute
the command and here we getting this of a credential, which I have given, okay, this one
of a credential, okay, you can see the GitHub repo and as a access and the password is
deleted that I just removed the password, okay, it all will be saved in the password manager
so you can see the private run zero and password here, it's an AJAY, AJAY123, it's not
an actual password, so here you can see the same username and password here, so this
is how you can grip the credential from the Chrome, I will be giving the both of the command,
okay, both of those command there, so don't worry about that the browser credential dumping,
okay, so hope you have enjoyed this video, let's break out and we'll connect it next
to you guys, bye bye!